さて ここは　島のどの辺だろうな。 とりあえず 「アカンパニー」パクって
The ability he's using to separate
Pouf from the King.
どっか飛ぶか？
If the third floor of the tower
is surrounded by smoke, the King and Pitou aren't there.
招かれざる客か。
Where are they?
ジャンケン　グ！
Gon...
ビスケ どうやったら「念」を飛ばせるの？
Grandpa!
修行！ パは放出系か。
Which means that that's...
ズバっ！と 岩とか切りたいんだけど…。 なるほど なかなか理にかなってるわね。
the King!
発想はガキだけど
Proceed.
拳に「念」を込める時 どうしても時間がかかるでしょ？
I am fully aware that you seek
to accomplish your objective
その間を埋める　いい方法がないか 考えたんだけど
with minimal human casualties.
ジャンケンの話を聞いた時 ピンと来たんだ。 俺　ジャンケン好きだし。
You took advantage of the chaos in the palace
うん　その直感は　とても重要よ。
in order to separate my Royal Guard from me.
念能力の とりわけ　特殊技ってのは
It makes no difference.
フィーリングが大事なの。 自分に合ってるって認識がね。
Proceed.
充電すれば　結構　電力上がるぜ。 すっごいや　キルア！ 電気ウナギみたい！
Dragon Head!
例え悪ぃぞ。
He is frightening...
この年で　オーラを 電気に変化させるなんて
The technique he unleashed was
not intended to hurt the King.
恐ろしい…
And both of them could tell that the King
でも　それ以上に　悲しい子
realized this at once.
日常が地獄だったはず 今　こうして笑顔でいられるのが 奇跡的なほどの…
Zeno made certain that his Nen
was completely neutral. Was it a gesture of respect? Or was it...
せっかく　修行が 面白くなって来たとこなのになぁ。
Killua...
試験の申し込みは 確か年内までだわさ。 急がなくっちゃ！
Pitou is over there.
外に出るスペルカードくらい あるんじゃね？
Let's go!
さて どっかで　お茶しようかしらね。
Let's go...
とりあえず　店で聞いてみるか。 国外に出る方法？
In what sense did you mean that?
なら３０００ジェニーになるぜ。 うん。 うん。 西へ５０ｋｍぐらい行くと この国唯一の港があるんだが
Killua barely managed to stop himself
from asking the question.
その港の所長を倒すか 裏金を　たっぷり渡さないと
If I ask that question, I won't be able to stop anymore...
国外へ行くチケットは もらえない。
I won't be able to go back.
所長の気分次第。 なるほど。 あとは　「リーブ」のスペルカードを 使うしかないが
If Killua would just ask, he would have his answer.
これが　なかなかレアでね。 どうする？ 港へ行こう。
Anyone with enough experience
would easily arrive at that next step.
レアカードだから　いくら買っても 出ないケースだってあり得る。
But the fear of losing someone he cared for
確かに。
prevented him from taking that step.
それじゃ　即行で合格して 戻って来るぜ。 ドーレ港の裏山にある 一本杉の下に
A few moments before the dragon took flight, Cheetu and Brovada appeared
キリコって魔獣が　すんでるから
before Ikalgo.
俺の友達だって言えば 会場まで連れてってくれるよ。
Hey, it's Flutter.
いらっしゃい。
I just returned...
スタートと同じ場所？
It seems the enemy is attacking.
いや　違うな あの女と似てるけど… まっ ゲームじゃ　よくあること
Seriously? Well, I couldn't imagine anything else causing this.
島から出るのですね？　それでは 行き先を決めてください。
What happened to your wings? Oh, uh...
ドーレ港ってある？ はい　ございます。
I lost them earlier, during the attack. Are you going underground?
んじゃ　それで。 かしこまりました。
Y-Yeah, I have orders from Hagya-sama.
この島を出ますと
What should we do?
フリーポケットのカードデータは 消滅してしまいますが よろしいですか？ 大丈夫　平気。
Well, we weren't told to defend this place...
それでは　またのご来島を お待ちしております。
But I'm just itching to try my new technique.
試験　申し込んだら 一本杉　目指すか
That looks fun!
その前に シャワーと着替えだな
I'm gonna check it out! Be careful!
さぁ　走りながら修行　修行！
I'm gonna see what's going on!
０から９までの数字を １分以内に作れたらクリアよ。
Then, I'll be going. Okay.
まずは　話を聞いてくれ。
Meanwhile, in the throne room,
in the central tower...
恐らくは　ブラフであろう 奴らの条件を信じてな。
Is it truly possible
何とか…　ならないの？ 犠牲を覚悟の上なら…。
to trap me in one place?
無理だな 確実に犠牲になるのは 奴らに 最初に飛びかかる何人か。
Why don't we find out?
そんな役を誰が望む？
Wing scales...
確かに。 最も 戦闘技術に長けたジスパーが
Knov said that they can hypnotize people.
目の前で　あっさり　やられた。
I don't want to inhale any...
奴を　むざむざゲーム外へ 逃がしたのも致命的だった。
You seem to be finished talking. I would expect that of anyone
with considerable power.
それぞれが 所持していたカードと
However...
恥ずかしい話　俺自身 奴が「リーブ」を唱える瞬間まで あの場の空気に のまれていたんだ。
Caution, resolve, and confidence in a 2:3:5 ratio.
相手の説明を 理解しようとすることで 頭が　いっぱいだったのね。
His caution isn't as strong
because he's confident.
ああ　全く前情報のない状態から 奴のペースに　はまれば
It's safe to say he has a strong personality.
恐らく　心理的に 作動を阻止するてはない。
Pouf's Spiritual Message
でも　何で　この話を私達に？ 俺が　この島で会った者の中で 君らが 最も頼りになると思ったからさ。
surrounds his opponent with wing scales,
making their aura more opaque, letting him sense their state of mind.
君達も 他のプレーヤーに会ったら ボマーについての情報を 教えてやってくれ。
I suppose I should introduce myself.
カラクリさえ分かっていれば 対策は立つはず。 そして　できることなら 俺達の敵を討ってほしい！
I am Shaiapouf, one of the King's Royal Guard.
少なくとも　決して　奴らに ゲームクリアなんて　させないでくれ！ うん！ 分かったわ。
His caution has increased slightly.
俺も　残りの時間で
You won't tell me your name?
なるべく多くの者に ボマーの情報を伝える。
If you believe that I'm trying
ブック！ 「リターン」オン　ブンゼン！
to trick you into inhaling my wing
scales, you're sadly mistaken.
俺が「マグネティックフォース」で 会えるプレーヤーは あいつらだけだったんだ
After a rebirth, all will be forgotten.
もしも　奴らの言う一斉解除が 実は　一斉爆破だとしたら…
I'll need you to wait a moment.
ようやく　おでましか。 さぁ　指輪をよこせ。
If he wants to waste time, that's fine by me. No matter what sort of beast he emerges as...
フン…　サブ　はめとけ。 ゲーム外で もう１個　指輪をはめちまうと データが上書きされちまうんだ。
Shoot was fighting recklessly,
without concern for his life, which turned out to be the
reason he was still alive.
さて　それじゃあ 一緒に　中に戻るか。
Hotel Rafflesia...
えっと　お前　誰だっけ？ クッ…。
While barely dodging multiple attacks that
would have been otherwise lethal, Shoot had only managed to take
the eye on Youpi's shoulder.
ミガームラ　サミンガードゥラ インテラミンガ　ゼンベラルブラ。
He had essentially done no damage.
森の精霊よ　我に取りつきし 不浄の念を取り去りたまえ。
However...
さて…　鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
The strange sensation that his momentum
was being stolen, rather than stopped, influenced Youpi's mental state tremendously.
森の精霊の力を借り 俺の具現化能力と合わせ
After taking multiple hits from
attacks he didn't understand, Youpi was backing up.
他人の放った念能力を食う 念獣をつくり出す！
I can't let this guy near the King.
デカい…　やはりボマーの 「カウントダウン」は
Every second I keep him away
from the King counts.
相当強い「念」…
Youpi and Shoot shared the same objective.
どうなったんだ？ 解除は　まだか!?
However, this expected turn of events
ブック！
was difficult on Knuckle...
ほぉ…　指定ポケット８１種
Hold it in...
確かに　受け取った。
I can't attack now!
さぁ　条件通りにしたぞ！ 爆弾を解除してくれ！ もちろんだ　約束は守る。
If I attack now, I'll be broadcasting
だが　その前に 「リーブ」のカードを３枚くれ。
that there's one more enemy
he needs to worry about!
ＯＫ　取引成立だ　サブ　バラ。
Hold it in!
リリース！
Hold it in... Please hold it in!
うわ！
Knuckle was unable to hold back the
tears streaming down his face.
ハッハッハ…　解放してやったぜ
Only ten seconds have passed?
恐怖からな。
You're kidding!
ハハハ…！ や…　約束が…。
How much longer do I have to endure
this suffocating, excruciating wait
あ？　守るわきゃねえだろ。
that makes me want to do nothing but run away?
てめぇら　クズとの約束なんてよ。
This must be some kind of joke...
リリースは解除じゃなく 起爆の合図さ。
And it isn't funny!
ふぅ…。
I can't hold it in any longer!
だが　こいつは　ゲンスルーがかけた 念能力の解除条件を満たすか
Knuckle's rampage was halted
奴が死ぬまで 消えることはない
by the first tap from Meleoron.
厄介なパートナーが できちまったな
Seriously?! It's only been ten seconds!
こら！　動くな！
But that just might have saved me.
ボマーは　俺達を全て始末する… したと思い込むはず
Meleoron wasn't trying to help Knuckle.
そこが　つけ目！
He, too, had reached his limit.
ビスケ…。
Crap!
ん？
Uh-oh.
やっぱり　一度　彼らの アジトに行ってみようよ。
He barely scratched me, but it
was enough damage
もう時間切れのはず。 何より　詳しい場所さえ 聞いてないんだわよ？
to offset the interest and
my full-strength attack.
仮に場所が分かっても 行くのに必要なスペルカードは １枚も持ってないわさ。 分かってる　でも　もしかしたら
Shoot is risking his life out there, while I'm standing here unhurt,
and making stupid mistakes!
爆発で死んでない人も いるかもしれないでしょ？ いないわね 標的に気づかれることなく 爆弾を 取り付けることができるのに
Youpi felt no sensation of scratching anything, nor did he notice APR's declaration
of returned interest.
そんなミスは　しないわさ。
Damn!
ただ…　ボマーは ゲームを続けていれば
He couldn't hear Knuckle's scream, either.
ぶつかる可能性の高い相手。
Calm down, you fool...
そういう意味じゃ アジトへは　近い時期に 行く必要があるかもしれない。
You're gonna ruin everything.
うん。 スペルカードがいるわね。
Here's the distance where we want to stay...
マサドラで怪物カード換金して スペルカード買う？
Not close enough for him to find us,
but close enough to get in fast.
うん！
He'll notice APR for a second,
but that's no problem.
ねぇ　ビスケ　俺の必殺技 どのくらいで完成すると思う？ あんたの「念」は まだまだ発展途上。 威力もスピードも ピークは分からない。
Shoot's fighting hard, so go ahead and catch your breath, Meleoron.
そう…。 ただし　へなちょこでも
God's Accomplice...
形が完成するのは そんな先のことじゃないわさ。
Undo.
そうだわね　ん…。
What is this thing?
キルアが戻るまでには 完成させておきたいわね！
When did it show up? No, it can't be that I didn't notice it.
よし！　絶対　完成して 驚かせてやるぞ！
It just suddenly appeared. Was I hit by an attack?
お客様　ラッキー！
So it must have been then!
彼らが集めてた スペルカードだ…
Does that mean the condition
was met during the fight?
２人で６０枚も買ったから 種類も　いろいろあるね。
What is this number? Is it a countdown? A bomb?
ん？　ちょっと…。 ん？　あっ！
No, the number isn't going up or down.
ランクＳ 限度枚数　たったの１０枚。
This is too much of a pain!
シ！　声が大きいわさ！ 怪しまれるでしょうが！
I only need to destroy the source!
う　こんな時 キルアがいればな ヘックション！
Something's coming. Despite his overwhelming power, one reason Youpi was unable to defeat Shoot
フンフン…　うん 確かに　ゴンのにおいがする。
was the evident difference in
skill level between them.
試験会場までの案内は　任せな。
It's fast... I can't get away!
パっと行って サっと合格して
One skewered chunk of meat coming up!
その間　ゴンとあんたの話を 聞かせておくれ。
He hit himself to accelerate.
ＯＫ！　じゃ　あいつが俺ん家 来た時の話でもしようか。
Very well... That was close.
ハッ！ 非常に順調だわよ。
Youpi's analysis was on the mark.
必殺技も 予定通りに行きそうだわね。 ここなら安心して 修行できるからね。
It was true that Youpi was
increasingly likely to win this fight.
少なくとも　攻撃スペルの 射程範囲に誰かが来たら
If he made any mistake, it was not realizing
すぐに分かるし。 スタート地点の時と同じような 監視されてる視線を
that Shoot was fine with this fact.
次。
I...
あっ！　ダメだ　全然　届かないよ。
I'm not done...
よいよい　変化系に比べたら 格段に筋がいいだわさ。
However, quietly and surely...
焦らず　まずは放たれた 球状のオーラを
Shoot was reaching his limit.
この修行に慣れれば あんたの「纏」なら オーラの球を　２３日ぐらい 宙に浮かせ続けられるわよ。
Hey, Youpi!
あのくらいの距離も 今日中には届くわさ。
Over here, fool!
あっ　ホントだ！　届いた！ 早っ！
Knuckle!
毎日　真面目に「纏」と「練」を こなしてる証拠だわねぇ んじゃ　また基礎練に戻るわよ！
I'm telling him that there's one
more enemy to worry about?
オス！
That's fine.
必殺技習得のため ビスケとの修行を重ねるゴン ハンター試験を受けるため 一度ゲームから出たキルア
That will serve to distract Youpi, and it will save Shoot.
２人は それぞれの目標に向かって
Bring it!
突き進むのだった
After calming down and regaining composure, Knuckle decided to show himself.